{
    "subject": "resource/Whitworth_University",
    "predicate": "ontology/athletics",
    "object": "resource/NCAA_Division_III",
    "human_readable": "Whitworth University participates in NCAA Division III athletics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9676802158355713,
            "question": "What are the benefits of participating in Division III athletics for Whitworth University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.961771547794342,
            "question": "Are there any notable achievements by Whitworth University's NCAA Division III athletes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9349101781845093,
            "question": "What division of NCAA athletics does Whitworth University participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8852205276489258,
            "question": "Is Whitworth University involved in college sports?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8751726746559143,
            "question": "In which NCAA division would you find Whitworth University's athletic teams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8060972690582275,
            "question": "What athletic programs are offered at Whitworth University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7163180112838745,
            "question": "Does Whitworth University have a strong athletic presence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6563460826873779,
            "question": "At what level of NCAA competition does Whitworth University compete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6286118626594543,
            "question": "What are some of the rivalries faced by Whitworth University in its division?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.621466875076294,
            "question": "How does Whitworth University's athletic program contribute to the overall student experience?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Whitworth University participates in NCAA Division III athletics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5490_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the rivalries faced by Whitworth University in its division?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5490_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=At what level of NCAA competition does Whitworth University compete?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5490_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Whitworth University have a strong athletic presence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5490_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5490_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5490_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5490_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5490_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5490_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5490_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5490_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5490_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5490_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5490_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Whitworth University participates in NCAA Division III athletics.\" For instance, document 114.txt mentions Whitworth Athletics being affiliated with the National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) at the division III level and participating in various sports."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}